http://www.ohmspeaker.com/privacy/

Skip to navigationSkip to content PrivacyYour privacy is critically important to us. At Ohm Acoustics we have a few fundamental principles:We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Ohm Acoustics collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Ohm Acoustics’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Ohm Acoustics’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Ohm Acoustics may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Ohm Acoustics’ websites choose to interact with Ohm Acoustics in ways that require Ohm Acoustics to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Ohm Acoustics gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who submit a product inquiry form to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with Ohm Acoustics – by placing a pre-order for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Ohm Acoustics collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Ohm Acoustics. Ohm Acoustics does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationOhm Acoustics discloses potentially personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Ohm Acoustics’ behalf or to provide services available at Ohm Acoustics’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Ohm Acoustics’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Ohm Acoustics will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Ohm Acoustics discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Ohm Acoustics believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Ohm Acoustics, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Ohm Acoustics website and have supplied your email address, Ohm Acoustics may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Ohm Acoustics and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Ohm Acoustics takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Ohm Acoustics uses cookies to help Ohm Acoustics identify and track visitors, their usage of Ohm Acoustics’ website, and their website access preferences. Ohm Acoustics visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Ohm Acoustics’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Ohm Acoustics’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf Ohm Acoustics, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Ohm Acoustics goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Ohm Acoustics may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Ohm Acoustics may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Ohm Acoustics’s sole discretion. Ohm Acoustics encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a CompanyDomain.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.SidebarSearchNews CategoriesNewsArticlesAdvicePhilosophyEventsNews & Views LatestPopularTagsArchive
Sep 12 2019 RMAF 2019 Wrap UpThe Rocky Mountain International Audio Fest (RMAF) was a different kind of show Ohm Speaker this …
Sep 09 2019 Spaced Out at RMAFThere was a lot to see at the 16th Annual Rocky Mountain International Audio Fest (RMAF). The …
Aug 16 2019 Brand New Walsh 2000s Available to Audition in GermanyThe Walsh 2000 Tall has been called the “Best Speaker Ever!!” by Z Reviews. And now for …
Feb 24 2015 DampingTo many consumers, damping speakers means “Clean with a moist cloth”; but that is …
Mar 15 2016 Your Ohm or Mine? Identifying Legacy OhmsThis week I received a call from a woman who had inherited a pair of Ohms from her uncle. She …
Jul 18 2017 Music and the Wholly Ohm-in’ EmpireDear Reader:
There are many secrets – acoustic and otherwise – in the realm known as the …amplifiersplacementwalshspikesvinyltechnologyqualitytestingimagingdesignhistoryhome theaterphysicsampspsychoacousticsmusichearingAtmosDolbylive musiccoherencecrossoverSBAbassphasemaintenanceDSPequalizationupgradesdispersionsensitivityefficiencyimpedanceauditiondemonstrationRMAFaudio showGermanyTrade Shows2019 September (2 posts)2019 August (2 posts)2019 July (1 posts)2019 May (1 posts)2019 April (1 posts)2019 February (1 posts)2019 January (1 posts)2017 November (1 posts)2017 September (1 posts)2017 July (1 posts)2017 June (2 posts)2017 May (3 posts)2017 April (2 posts)2017 March (2 posts)2017 February (2 posts)2017 January (2 posts)2016 December (2 posts)2016 November (2 posts)2016 October (2 posts)2016 September (2 posts)2016 August (3 posts)2016 July (2 posts)2016 June (2 posts)2016 May (2 posts)2016 April (2 posts)2016 March (3 posts)2016 February (2 posts)2016 January (2 posts)2015 December (2 posts)2015 November (2 posts)2015 October (2 posts)2015 September (3 posts)2015 August (2 posts)2015 July (2 posts)2015 June (2 posts)2015 May (2 posts)2015 April (2 posts)2015 March (5 posts)2015 February (4 posts)2015 January (4 posts)2014 December (5 posts)2014 November (4 posts)2014 October (4 posts)2014 September (5 posts)2014 August (4 posts)2014 July (5 posts)2014 June (4 posts)2014 May (4 posts)2014 April (4 posts)2014 January (1 posts)2013 May (1 posts)2013 February (2 posts)2011 November (1 posts)ReviewsA spacious acoustic ambience is linked with a ''reachout-and-touch-it'' immediacy that this listener has experienced only with the very best speakers.The Walsh 3000 upgrade has more than met my expectations so, those folks who are sitting the fence wondering whether or not upgrade, do so, you won’t be disappointed.The sound is everywhere. Everything you hear from these speakers comes from the entire front of your room.every time I turn the system on, even after six months, I am impressed all over again.Hans FantelFred from British ColumbiaZeosMike LLike us on FacebookFollow UsExploreTechnologyHistoryNewsReviewsHelp & SupportSupport Home120 Day TrialContact Usback to top
